本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigamiorg)制作仅供交流学习禁止用于任何商业用途
Man, it's crazy how we played more than sixty sets and only won three.
いやしかし６０セト以上やて
日听：小伍King翻译：森罗小江校对：Syura时间轴：海底压制：Coolkid
今のところ勝たのが３セトとは
Manabu! Come on, drink up.
学ほらもと飲め
We've walked quite a difficult road.
茨の道を来たもんですねぇ
No, thanks. If I drink any more, I'll definitely feel it tomorrow.
いやこれ以上飲むと明日に響くので
That's for sure.
確かにな
It won't affect us!
響かない
Though if they played like they did in the Seijou match,
we could've won a few more sets.
まぁもし青城戦の時のあいつらなら
もう少し勝てただろうけどな
Manabu, are you saying you're too good for my sake?
The team's offense was focused around Hinata and Kageyama's deviant fast attack and their bait routine,
日向影山の変人速攻と囮を軸にした烏野の攻撃スタイルとして
No, um...
I'm just kidding!
それなりに纏まていたからな
and they executed it well.
But the limits of that strategy were in sight.
でもそれだと限界が見えていた
And they hit that limit when they lost to Seijou.
現に青城には負けた
That's why they started changing things up.
だから新しいことを始めた
I know.
わかてますよ
今はそれぞれが「歯車」を作てる最中
Right now, they're each making their own gear.
It's still a work in progress, and they stand no chance against a powerhouse team from Kanto.
全てが未完成で関東の強豪に勝てるはずもない
でも歯車が噛み合たら
But if those gears all line up...
Hey! Don't think that you'll win against Nekoma that easily!
音駒に簡単に勝てると思うなよぉ
簡単にだなんてそんな
Easily? I would never think that!
満を持して勝ちます
But we'll be eagerly looking for the chance to win!
You sure talk big now, Takeda.
言うようになたな先生
You too, Ukai!
愉快じゃの
Karasuno               Fukurodani
This is the final set.
これが最後の１セト
We've been losing this entire training camp.
負けぱなしのこの遠征
Let's try to rip at least one set away from the most powerful team at this training camp, Fukurodani,
せめてこの合宿メンバ中最強の梟谷から
before going home!
１セト捥ぎ獲て帰ろうや
しゃあ
Yeah!
合宿の成果見せてやる
I'll show you the results of this training camp!
Episode Ten:
Gears
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Let's have a good match!
お願いします
一本取るぞ
Let's get this point!
Yeah!
All right! Bring it, Karasuno!
しゃぁ来いや烏野
Give us a good serve, Asahi!
旭さんナイサ
It's a bit off!
乱した
Bokuto!
木兎さん
Right!
シャア
Left! Number four!
レフト４番
Tighten up for the straight spike.
ストレト締めろよ
It'll get through if there's even the tiniest gap.
少しでも隙があると抜かれる
It's out!
アウト
よしゃ
Yes!
Damn, it went out of bounds.
ブロクアウトか
So close!
惜しい
Don't worry about it, Tsukishima! You almost had it!
日に日に育つてハラ立つわ
ドンマイ月島よくやたぞ
It really pisses me off how you guys keep improving day by day.
Right.
Left, left!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
レフトレフト
Whoa, he got it!
拾た
でも乱した
But it's way off course!
A fast attack from there?!
あそこから速攻
Even if the receive is a little off,
they confidently pull off a fast attack.
多少レシブが乱れても強気で速攻使てきやがる
Their setter's pretty skilled too.
向こうのセタも相当やるな
ナイサ
Give us a good serve.
Stop them here!
一本で切れ
Their number four is up front now.
４番前衛に上がてきた
やと前で打てるぜ
Now I can finally hit up front.
Give us a good one!
ナイサ
Nishinoya!
西谷
Nice receive!
ナイスレシブ
Nice, Saru!
ナイス猿
Let me finish it off!
ラスト寄こせ
今うちの前衛は一番壁の高いロテだ
Our current rotation has the tallest wall of blocks in the front row.
Make sure you stop the ball!
一本止めてみせろ
That's an insane cut shot.
なんつ超インナに打てくるんだ
A strong hit that cuts in front of three blockers is very difficult to execute.
３枚ブロクの更にインナへの強打は凄く難しいの
It can be hard on your shoulders if they're not flexible.
肩が柔らかくないと負担も掛かるしね
All right!
おおしゃぁ
Did you see that, Akaashi?
見た赤葦
Hey, did you see my awesome cut shot just now?
ねぇ今の俺の超インナスパイク見た
I did. It was amazing.
見ました凄いですね
It was pure luck, though!
まぐれだけど
木兎うるせぇな
Bokuto is so annoying.
すげなまぐれでも
That's amazing, even if it was luck.
I'd love to hit a spike like that.
打てみてぇ
あの梟谷の木兎君は不思議ですね
Bokuto from Fukurodani is a truly strange player.
Hey, can I try hitting that again?
なあもう一回打てもいいかな打ちてぇ
Even when he's your opponent,
you kind of want to cheer for him.
敵であろうと賞讃の拍手を送りたくなる選手というか
I wanna do it again!
The other team's completely on to you, Bokuto.
相手にバレバレですよ木兎さん
Though I think that might be because he's on a completely different level.
格上と思てしまているからかもしれませんが
Oh crap! My bad.
そうかしまたじゃぁストレト狙うか
Maybe I'll go for a straight spike, then.
Yeah...
確かに
He might just be a player who lifts the spirits of both his teammates and his opponents.
敵味方関係なく士気を高めてしまう選手かもな
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Yeah!
月島ナイサ
Give us a good serve, Tsukishima!
A special attack?!
必殺技
Yep!
おうよ
Listen closely. This attack is best described as something born from upsetting the balance of stillness and motion.
いいかこの技はな言うなれば静と動による揺さぶりだ
Whoa! Whoa...
またカコ良さげに言う
There he goes, trying to sound all cool again.
Do you have any clue what he's talking about?
お前何のことかわかんの
I have an idea.
予想がつきます
This attack isn't something you use to run away from the enemy.
この技はな逃げるために使うもんじゃねぇ
With perfect timing, a perfect set, a perfect position for spiking...
完璧なタイミング完璧なトス完璧なスパイクの体勢
Just when everyone thinks a powerful spike is incoming...
強烈なスパイクが来ると誰もが思た時
And more than anything, the moment when you think
you can land a powerful shot is the perfect opportunity!
何より自分が強烈な一発が打てると思た瞬間が好機
I got this!
任せろ
ナイスレシブ
Nice receive!
Like you're laughing at them, really go for it!
嘲笑うように
カマセ
Ah!
Hinata just...
日向が
tipped it over!
フェイント
When the tip succeeds, there's a great feeling
that's totally different than when you land a spike.
フェイントが決まるとな
スパイク決めた時と違う気持ち良さがあんだよ
前に落ちるボルを拾いにレシバが数人飛び込んでくるだろ
You know how a few people will dive for the falling ball?
Yeah.
今まで自分と同じかそれ以上にあた目線が
You're usually eye level with them or higher, but when they try to reach for the ball, miss, and then look up...
ボルギリギリ届かずこちを見上げる瞬間が
It's the best feeling.
最高なんだよ
A tip?!
フェイントだと
木兎さんが教えたんじゃないですか
You're the one who taught it to him.
You actually used your head?
お前アタマ使たのか
You're gonna get a fever.
熱出るぞ
You're the only one who doesn't get to say stuff like that to me.
ホントお前にだけは言われたくね
Hmph!
I won't let them score another point!
もうあいつらには１点もやんねぜ
I think it's impossible to completely shut them out.
１点もやらないのはムリだと思います
Back me up once in a while, Akaashi!
赤葦たまにはのてきて
Damn you, Shorty!
クソォオチビちゃんめ
We're not gonna lose!
こちも負けねぞ
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Number two!
２番２番
All right!
Ready, and...
They all seem to be enjoying themselves.
皆心無しか調子がいいように見えますね
I touched it!
ワンタチ
Got it!
オライ
I wonder if Bokuto has something to do with it.
木兎君に感化されたかな
Wow, a setter dump!
よしゃ
ツアタク
Kageyama is doing well too!
影山君もいいですねぇ
His jump serves have been on point.
ジャンプサブも今日はミスありませんし
Yeah, he's really calm and collected today.
ああ今日の影山なんつか
落ち着いてるつか穏やかだよな
It scary like the calm before the storm.
嵐の前の静けさみたいな怖さがあるな
Give us another good serve, Tsukishima!
月島もう一本ナイサ
I feel like everything I ate this morning is gone from my stomach, yet I'm still not hungry.
朝食た物が腹に無くなた感じがする
でもまだ腹は空かない
My body's more responsive than usual,
and I can clearly see what everyone else is doing.
いつもより体がよく動くし周りの動きもよく見える
Even I can tell I'm playing well today.
自分の調子がいいことが自分でわかる
All right!
The same goes for everyone else.
他の人もそうだ
ナイス大地さん
Nice, Daichi!
Is it because of the barbecue?
バベキュ効果か
Hinata's doing well too.
日向の調子もいい無駄な動きもない
He's making no unnecessary movements.
今なら
We just might
新しい速攻が使えるかもしれない
be able to do the new fast attack.
But...
旭さんナイスレシブ
Nice receive, Asahi!
あの速攻やる気か
Is he planning on doing the new fast attack?
If we mess it up, we could destroy the good mood the team has developed.
でも今ミスすればチムのいい空気を壊すかもしれない
新しい速攻はもと成功率を上げてからに
We should hold off until the chance of success is higher.
You're not gonna do it?
やんねの
The ball comes...
ボル来る
and then...
そんで
it stops.
止まる
Wait! What the hell was that?!
てふざけんなやるなら先に言とけ
If we're gonna do that, tell me beforehand!
I just felt like we could pull it off! Didn't you feel it too?!
だて今イケルて感じしたろしたろ
I did, but it was too sudden!
したけど突然過ぎる
なんだあの変な速攻復活か
What the hell? Is that weird fast attack back?
Not quite.
I've gotta mentally prepare and stuff!
違います
心の準備とか色々あるだろうが
It's fine since we totally nailed it, right?!
That was different from the fast attack they did before.
いいじゃねぇか決めたし
今のは初期にやてたあの速攻とは別物ですよ
よくねえんだよ
Wrong!
C'mon! Let's do it again!
もかいやろうぜ
The first gear
歯車
is in place.
一つ目
!!
Haikyuu
Second Season
!!
Haikyuu
Second Season
The ball comes...
ボル来る
and then...
そんで
止まる
it stops.
Karasuno                    Fukurodani
All right!
よしゃああ
何だ今のオイすげな
All right!
What the heck was that?! It was awesome!
ナイス日向影山
Nice job, Hinata, Kageyama!
Hey, Akaashi. Was it really that amazing?
なあ赤葦今のそんなすげの
Could we do it too?
俺達もやれる
That's something we should never try.
あれはお手本にしちゃいけないモンですよ
日向は平然と打てますけど
Hinata hit it like it was nothing,
but I think that set is really hard to hit unless you're used to it.
相当慣れないと打ち辛いと思いますよあのトス
Not to mention,
あとそもそも
making a set float at the point of impact is incredible. I couldn't do it.
打点で止めるなんて神業俺には技術的にムリです
You're not gonna do it?
やんねの
He dragged me along again. Dammit.
またこいつに引張られたクソ
What? You wanna start somethin'?
なんだよやんにょかコラ
でもスゲなスゲ
That was awesome! So cool!
目の前で止またぞこうシュルて
It stopped right before my eyes!
It was like, "shoop"!
I was totally sure it was gonna finally work!
今回は絶対来る感じしたけど
実際目の前で止まるとビビるな
But when it actually stopped in front of my eyes, it freaked me out!
You really are amazing!
やぱりお前スゲな
Wh-What're you saying, you moron...
なんなんだボケェ
Amazing! You're so amazing!
The look on Kageyama's face defies description.
影山がなんとも形容し難い顔になてる
You're so awesome, Kageyama!
スゲ影山
ヤメロボケェ
What's up with his facial muscles?
表情筋どうした
It's not often that Hinata praises Kageyama in a straightforward manner.
日向が影山をストレトに褒めるてなかなかないもんなぁ
もう一回やるよあれ
信じて待ててよかたな
I'm glad we actually believed in this and waited.
Yeah.
とにかく次はちゃんと
Anyway, next time, make sure you—
You did it!
You did it! You did it!
やたやたぁ
Nice spike, Hinata, Kageyama!
ナイスキ日向影山君
約３週間ぶり
They finally succeeded after three weeks.
Ever since that fight, Hinata and Kageyama haven't been on speaking terms.
あの喧嘩以来日向と影山君は口も利かなくなた
だけど二人はそれぞれの課題に直向きに取り組んできた
Yet they both worked hard on improving.
And now...
そして今
変人コンビ再起動だ
the deviant duo is back in action!
One more time!
もう一回
クソ羨ましい俺にも決めさせろ
I'm so jealous!
Let me look cool too!
負けてらんないな
We can't let them beat us.
続くぞ
Let's keep it up!
ヘイヘイヘイのまれるんじゃねぇぞお前ら
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't get cocky, you guys!
All right!
よしゃ
翔陽は
Shouyou...
always does something new.
いつも新しいね
If Shorty was on our team,
would you be a little more motivated?
もしチビちゃんがうちにいたら
お前ももうちょいやる気出すのかね
It'd be impossible to be on the same team as him.
翔陽と一緒のチムは無理
Huh? Why?
なんで
常に新しくなていかなくちゃ翔陽についていけなくなる
I wouldn't be able to keep up with him
unless I kept coming up with something new.
No matter how cleverly I ditched practice, I'm pretty sure he'd notice.
俺がどんなに上手にサボてもたぶん翔陽にはバレる
That first-year setter prodigy hesitated for just a second and Shouyou figured it out.
あの天才一年セタでさえ
一瞬立ち止まただけで見抜かれた
That'd be exhausting.
そんなの疲れるじゃん
I see.
じゃあチビちゃんが敵として練習相手にいてくれたら
Then would you be properly motivated
if he was your opponent during practice?
お前もちゃんとやる気出すのか
What do you mean?
なんで
Because when you watch him play,
your face looks like it does after you buy a new game.
だてお前チビちゃんの試合見てる時
買てきた新しいゲム始める時みたいな顔してるよ
別にしてないし
No, it doesn't.
Actually, what does that face even look like?
ていうかそれどんな顔
Really excited.
わくわく顔
What the heck? I don't know what you're talking about.
何それ意味分かんない
I don't make that face.
してないし
You do.
してるし
I do not.
してないし
You do.
してる
してない
I do not.
U-Um, Ukai?
ああの烏養くん
正直ぱと見では
To be honest, at first glance, I can't tell the difference between that and the old deviant fast attack.
前の変人速攻との違いが分からないんですが
Oh.
前の速攻は日向の打点をズバと通過するトス
In the previous fast attack, the set would go right through Hinata's point of impact.
Point of
Impact
Conversely, with this new fast attack,
それに対して新しい速攻はスパイカの最高打点イコル
Point of
Impact
they're trying to make it so that the spiker's highest point of impact is in the same place as the ball's point of arrival.
ボルの最高到達点にしようとしてるんだ
Once the ball's forward momentum dies,
ボルの前に進む力が死んで落ちる瞬間
there's a brief moment that you wouldn't have if the ball was going straight through.
ボルが通過してた時より一瞬の余裕ができる
その一瞬があることが決定的な差だ
That one moment existing is the difference.
It means Hinata has more options while mid-air.
空中で日向の選択肢が増える
Oh!
I gotta bring the old man to the spring tourney prelims.
春高の予選は絶対じじいを連れてこなきゃな
こいつらの速攻生で見せてやる
I'll show him their fast attack up close!
Nice receive!
ナイスレシブ
Kill the ball's momentum.
ボルの勢いを殺す
Kill it!
殺す
クソさきとイメジは一緒なのに
Shit! And everything looked the same as last time too!
All right!
よしゃあ
Oh my.
We got lucky!
Did he lose his incredible concentration from earlier?
先までの神がかり的な集中は途切れちゃたかな
Shake it off, Kageyama!
影山くんドンマイ
That really pisses me off!
クソ腹立つ
Why's that? Besides, what else was I supposed to say?!
なんでだよそれ以外に言いようねぇだろ
Well, it's not something you can always expect to go perfectly...
まあそうそううまく行くもんでもないよな
そんな時こそ
And what better time...
...for the upperclassmen to shine!
先輩の出番ですな
Karasuno               Fukurodani
One blocker!
ブロク一枚
ワンタチ
I touched it!
オライ
Got it!
There's that weird sound again!
したでもドリブルは取られてない
But a double hit wasn't called.
The libero's set...
リベロのトスから
エスの
leads to the ace's back row attack!
バクアタク
The second gear
歯車二つ目
is in place!
It's out?!
アウトか惜しい
That was so close!
Sorry, my set was a bit low! Damn it!
すんませんトス低かたチクショウ
I-It was great!
あいやよよかたよ
逆に今のは俺のミスだと思うし
I think that was more a mistake on my end.
Please say it sucks if it sucks!
だめなもんはだめて言わないとだめすよ旭さん
Oh, okay...
あはい
I-I'd be so happy if the set was a bit higher.
ももうちょとトスを高めにほしい
一週間でこんなに変わんのかよ怖ぇな
They changed this much in a week?
分かてますそんなこと
I know that!
Terrifying.
That's it! Keep it up!
それでいいぞガンガン行け
We still lack the experience to be able to go head-to-head with a powerhouse school while they're on guard.
護りに入て
強豪と渡り合えるだけの地力は俺たちにはまだない
Got it!
オライ
レフトレフト
Left! Left!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
Two blockers!
ブロク２枚
In order for us to win,
うちのチムが勝つためには
We have a chance here!
チャンスボル
ヘタクソだろうが
even if we suck...
We can score!
オライ
Got it!
新しい武器を磨くのみ
...all we should do is hone our new weapons!
Now!
今
Multiple spikers almost simultaneously
make their approach from several directions!
多方向から複数のスパイカがほぼ同時に助走へ
ファストテンポのシンクロ攻撃
A synchronized attack at first tempo!
The blockers can't narrow in on a target!
ブロクに的を絞らせるな
Everyone dives in, believing that the set will come to them!
全員がトスは自分にあがると信じて突込め
All right!
おしゃあああ
スパイクキマルマジキモチイイ
I nail spike... Seriously feel good...
He's crying.
All right!
よしゃ
泣いてる
He's babbling.
片言になてる
I mean, it's been a while since nailing a spike has felt this satisfying.
だてこんなに気持ちよく決まるの久々すもん
Dammit, they're attacking from every which way...
チクショウあちこちから攻撃しやがて
Nice set, Kageyama!
影山ナイストス
Thank you!
あざす
Nice spike, Tanaka!
田中くんナイスキ
あざす
Thanks!
Keep coming up with something new, huh?
常に新しくか
Stay focused!
余所見すんな
The third gear
歯車三つ目
is in place!
That was a synchronized attack at first tempo.
今のファストテンポのシンクロ攻撃
It went so smoothly!
綺麗に決まりましたね
Yeah.
ブロク３人に対して
Against their three blockers, our attack had four people advancing at once if you include the back row attack.
こちの攻撃はバクアタク含めて４人同時
They couldn't follow all of them.
マクし切れないからな
Is something wrong?
どうかしました
いやちょとやてみたいことができた
No.
There's just something I want to try out now.
Damn it!
Yes!
よしゃ
Karasuno's at the top of their game.
烏野好調だな
The messy attacks they were trying
on the first day are finally succeeding.
初日ぐずぐずだた攻撃が決まるようになてきてる
よしゃあ
All right!
Karasuno               Fukurodani
This is going great.
よしよしよし梟谷相手に終盤まで同点できたな
We're actually neck-and-neck with Fukurodani at the last part of the match.
Yeah!
だからといて浮かれんなよこからが勝負だ
Don't get overconfident.
The real battle begins now.
Yes, sir!
It's true that you shouldn't let your guard down.
確かに油断は禁物です
But it's also true that the gears you guys have created are starting to mesh with one another.
でも皆の作り上げた歯車が今噛み合いつつあるのは確か
この試合を戦う中で更に磨きをかけていてください
In the course of fighting out this set,
please work on honing them even further!
Yessir!
後今回は作戦通り
Also, our plan of not letting their ace have free reign is going well.
いい感じにあまり相手のエスに気持ちのいいスパイクを打たせてない
Well, except for that ridiculous cut shot.
一つとんでもねぇインナスパイクはあたけどな
But that was because Tsukishima got a hand on a spike earlier.
月島がワンタチとてるおかげだな
Oh, right.
あはい
If we can keep number four under control,
then victory is in sight.
４番を押さえられれば勝機が見えてくる
攻めて行くぞ
Let's finish this!
Yessir!
We're having a difficult time, but let's stay calm. We can't let Karasuno's attacks faze us.
苦戦してますがうちらは烏野の多彩な攻撃に惑わされずに
落ち着いてやていきましょう
Yeah!
Right.
Were you listening, Bokuto?
木兎さん話聞いてました
Yeah, of course I was listening!
聞いてたつの
C'mon, let's do this already.
ほらささと始めんぞ
Do you think that's...
あれてまさか
Karasuno                 Fukurodani
All right!
よしゃあ
Damn it! I'm sorry!
クソすんません逆転できるチャンスだたのに
That was our chance to turn things around too!
Don't worry about it!
ドンマイドンマイ
Nice try, Noya!
ノヤさんナイスファイト
All right, I'll leave them in the shadows with my serve!
おし俺のサブで突き放す
Give us a good one, Bokuto!
木兎ナイサ
Bokuto, stay calm.
木兎さん冷静にですよ
I am calm!
冷静だ
ああいかん熱くなりだしたか
This isn't good. He's losing his temper.
All right! Here I go!
しゃ行くぞほら
チクショウすまん
Damn it! I'm sorry!
Just calm down.
一回落ち着け
ドンマイです
Don't worry about it.
すまん
I'm sorry!
Karasuno                 Fukurodani
Hey, Karasuno caught up with them again.
おいおいまた追いついちまたぞ烏野
Yeah.
ああ最後の最後に大番狂わせか
Are they actually gonna turn the tables at the last minute?
向こうの４番はどからでも打てくる
Their number four can spike from any point on the court.
Let's aim for him with our serves to restrict his movement a little.
サブで狙て少しでも牽制すんぞ
Got it.
やべぇ端こ狙いすぎた
Crap! I aimed for the corner too hard!
You jerk!
こんにゃろ
Whoa, it barely made it in. I'm so lucky!
ギリ入たラキ
Give it to me!
俺に寄越せ一本で切てやる
I'll finish this in one hit!
Seconds
There are few outcomes when setting to Bokuto while he's a bit angry.
少し熱くなりすぎてる木兎さんにトスをあげた場合
Seconds
A: If he scores normally, then there's no problem.
Ａ普通に決まると問題なし
All right!
B: If he messes up or gets blocked again, he may start to feel even worse.
Ｂミスるまたはブロクされると
いつもより割増でテンションが下がる可能性あり
C: If I don't give him the ball...
Ｃあげなかた場合
ふんだもう知らない
Hmph! I don't care anymore!
...he may become uncooperative.
いじける恐れあり
C is the most annoying.
Ｃが一番面倒くさいな
木兎さん
Bokuto!
ブロク３枚
Three blockers!
All right!
しゃあ
Got it!
オライ
もう一回だ赤葦
Give it to me again, Akaashi!
お願いします
Here.
しゃあ
All right!
今度こそ止めるぞ
Let's stop him this time!
Ready, and...
All right!
しゃあ
Karasuno                 Fukurodani
Wow, Karasuno turned it around!
烏野逆転
Isn't this the first time they've been in the lead all week?
この一週間で烏野がリドしたの初めてじゃねぇか
I think you're right!
そうかも
W-Was that a block?
い今のはブロクですかね
No. It didn't go over the net, so it was a failed spike.
ううん今のはネトを越えなかたみたいだから
スパイクミスだね
Does this mean what I think it means?
もしかして
Oh boy. It's happening, isn't it?
あああれ来ちゃた
Really? This quickly?
嘘早くねぇ
Wow, already?
えもう
That was fast.
早いな
Jeez, here it comes.
ああ来た
Akaashi...
赤葦
今日はもう俺にはあげんな
Don't set for me anymore today!
There it is. Bokuto's depressed mode.
出た木兎しょぼくれモド
What the...
なんだ
Okay.
分かりました
Huh?
But in exchange, please calm down.
じゃあげない間に落ち着いてくださいね
Could this be our chance?
チャンス到来ですかね
Yeah, we can take this set!
ああ行けるぞこの試合
I don't know what's going on,
but their ace doesn't seem to be doing well!
よく分かんないけど向こうのエスが不調ぽい
畳み掛けるぞ
Let's keep it up!
Yeah!
しゃあ
Hinata, we're gonna use that fast attack again.
日向またあの速攻使てくぞ
I'll give you the set you want, so have faith in me and jump.
お前の欲しいトスをあげてやる
信じて跳べ
Okay!
We're going to take our new weapons
新しく手に入れたこの武器で
梟谷に勝つ
and defeat Fukurodani!
It looks like we can finally win against Fukurodani!
ついに梟谷に勝てそうだぞ
向こうのエス「俺にもうあげんな」とか言てたしなあ
Their ace was saying stuff like, "Don't set for me anymore!"
勝たほうがいぱい肉食えるのかな
Do you think the winner gets to eat more meat?
Wait, won't that mean we get to eat less if we lose?!
てことは負けたらあんま食えないてこと
We're absolutely gonna win this!
ぜてぇかつ
Episode Eleven:
"Up Above"
Next time on Haikyuu!!:
次回ハイキュ“上”
"'Up Above.'"